// Database Management System
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which type of data can be stored in the database?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Image oriented data",
      "Text, files containing data",
      "Data in the form of audio or video",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of database?.",
    answer: "Decentralized",
    options: [
      "Decentralized",
      "Distributed",
      "Hierarchical",
      "Network"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is a feature of DBMS?",
    answer: "Single-user Access only",
    options: [
      "Minimum Duplication and Redundancy of Data",
      "High Level of Security",
      "Single-user Access only",
      "Support ACID Property"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is a feature of the database?",
    answer: "User interface provided",
    options: [
      "No-backup for the data stored",
      "User interface provided",
      "Lack of Authentication",
      "Store data in multiple locations"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is not a function of the database?",
    answer: "Analysing code",
    options: [
      "Managing stored data",
      "Manipulating data",
      "Security for stored data",
      "Analysing code"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is known as a set of entities of the same type that share same properties, or attributes?",
    answer: "Entity set",
    options: [
      "Relation set",
      "Tuples",
      "Entity set",
      "Entity Relation model"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is information about data called?",
    answer: "Meta data",
    options: [
      "Meta data",
      "Tera data",
      "Hyper data",
      "Relations"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The ability to query data, as well as insert, delete, and alter tuples, is offered by _________",
    answer: "DML (Data Manipulation Langauge)",
    options: [
      "TCL (Transaction Control Language)",
      "DCL (Data Control Language)",
      "DDL (Data Definition Langauge)",
      "DML (Data Manipulation Langauge)"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "________ is a set of one or more attributes taken collectively to uniquely identify a record.",
    answer: "Super key",
    options: [
      "Primary Key",
      "Super key",
      "Candidate key",
      "Foreign key"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The top level of the hierarchy consists of ______ each of which can contain _____.",
    answer: "Catalogs, Schemas",
    options: [
      "Schemas, Catalogs",
      "Schemas, Environment",
      "Environment, Schemas",
      "Catalogs, Schemas"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which of the following fields would not make a suitable primary key ?",
    answer: "A data field",
    options: [
      "A data field",
      "An invoice number",
      "An auto number field",
      "A customer's social security number"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "RDBMS stands for",
    answer: "Relational Database Management System",
    options: [
      "Relational Database Management System",
      "Relation Data Mobile System",
      "Right Data Base Management System",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which command is used to add new rows to a table?",
    answer: "INSERT",
    options: [
      "ALTER TABLE",
      "ADD ROW",
      "INSERT",
      "APPEND"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which of the following is not a level of data abstraction?",
    answer: "Critical Level",
    options: [
      "Physical Level",
      "Critical Level",
      "Logical Level",
      "View Level"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "COUNT command's used to",

    answer: "count the number of records in an active database file",
    options: [
      "count the number of data fields in an active database file",
      "count the number of data files which are active",
      "count the records which are updated",
      "count the number of records in an active database file"
    ]
  },
];